Hello Hello Friends Welcome back to my
YouTube channel Now we
will look at ICICI Lombard Limited here In this
we will look at its fundamentals in short
and one because there is a technique behind it to
finalize the result From
which level can we take a U turn
and what will be its entry point So here
if we talk about it in technical terms then
technically it looks like a scattered attack here
ok here support here its level 10 is
seen and here in Noida let us first
look at some fundamentals here in short
So here for ICICI Lombard General
Insurance I have placed
stop here at 53.2
here it is placed high but when we
compare then we will come to know that
Aarushi is fine and the accused is looking fine here
If we go down here
and look at the peer comparison then the
stock of these insurance companies is also very
high ok very high
in comparison of that it has this thing right
here the stock cut is not much and
if we look at this bundle result  If we check,
we will see here that there is painting profit, we are
looking at operating profit, so the
last point and in that here - in
operating profit - 371, before that it was
in 400 line profit and before that we are looking at this
point,
then you saw a decline here, then since
when has the decline been happening, after September 2011, everyone,
we have seen since when the decline is happening here in the chart, it is
September 2010, we have
seen this technically in the chart, okay, so from here there was a
decline and then even now the decline has
increased a lot, hence we have seen a lot of profit here,
91, here
if we check the net profit Amritsar, then
here in this poster there was a decline, there was a
decline in the current quarter,
but here the extra income has been
shown to be very high, okay, hence here we are seeing
profit and once we will
see here, after the June quarter,
we had
seen a little more profit here,
after that again  There was a decline in the previous one,
this trend of decline is
continuing and what is happening in this,
okay, I mean there are more losses here
and profits are looking less, that is why
we are seeing a little bit of this here,
not a little, more soldiers, all this is being
seen and we will check one thing
here that what is the
role of the players here, let us
see, if you talk about the size, then from here they are
selling their goods, we
will see here, okay, there was freight, the
goods were sent again and the promoters are
selling their goods, so there will be
some here, that is why are the voters
selling the goods or if you look at it, they are
not very interested in it, as much
goods are already lying there, the last group dance is
written in it and public interest is
still there, so the chart here is
showing the age, okay, we have
seen fundamentally that here
we are seeing a little bit of decline, the results of the last two
quarters have
not been better than the previous quarters, hence
teachers here have been setting for the last five-six months  It is going on, right now the price has turned
left from it and it is
straightening out around 100, it has
cooled down, one thing we
will note here is that
if we
move its support zone here, then its
support zone will come approximately between 100 and ₹
10, okay, it will come between ₹10, so
look here now, it has come very close,
okay, it has come very close to its support, so it is
possible that it will rise
here in the coming time because if you
look here carefully, then it was a
value fund first, okay, in 2018, here,
you will see how much the fund has, before that, we
checked the range of this forty hundred
and how much it had gone to this extent, so we made it to one hundred,
next Sunday
Guardian Techcrunch made a comeback, so next
time the target level here will be good, we should
spend time here again
as we have done here the last two times,
okay, so here I feel that whatever is happening here,
Here,
before this Schezwan 1050, there will be a resistance.
Okay, after coming here, it will take some
time and form a range. After that, it will
decide whether to go above it or not. By going to
radiation, it will take a look at it once. By
going to retention, it will know right away.
Come, in the meantime, there has been a huge
fall between the last two short periods.
Here, this target of ₹1 has come
downwards and now it is
coming to its support zone. Okay, so
after falling so much here, it is possible that we may get a full
comeback here in the next week. In
this way, some ring channels can be formed.
Use the type here and
form a channel. It will go down to 11050 and then
trend upwards. So, in this way, some
channel formation can happen. I feel that
a part will go from here and that bag can be its
straight line. Come and
request again and this diamond will
form some range here between 1150 and 1150. Okay, these will be ranges and breakfast,
then downwards.  It will not be rooted,
as we saw, the time period before the
breakout occurred around winter.
Okay, so maybe we'll
test Z again. Here,
Mamta doesn't do best for Ujjain, so
if it respects the zero
level, then it will be like a straight line break.
Okay, as it will be one on the timeline,
we can create a position here in some quantity. We can take a
square slot and place it below and
then look at the time frame. If
we
look at Someshwar on the Sunday Times, there has been a
continuous decline here. So
here I think profit booking is going to happen
very soon. Like if we
search for 1118 buds,
we can see profit booking here. And
some such attack candles can be
seen here in the coming time or if it
opens at what, then you will become
incidental. In this way, some other missions can happen. So
in the coming time, if the
train line here is one and a half inch, then
what will we do here? Definitely, no one will be cowardly
like  Whatever it is made here,
okay, if there is a range printout like double title, then we
can do it here only,
Lal Singh's comment can be made, so a
range can be formed here or a straight line,
okay, so now what will we do,
keep the last minute stop loss and
close our position here, remember do
not do any trading without stars,
you should not trade any share from this, do
tell us how you liked the video in the comment section, if you want to ask any video question, then
some expert massage will be taken after this, we will meet
in the next video, if you liked the video then
please like, thank you